Guide to the W. Sterling Cole papers M2023
Special Collections and University Archives, Colgate University Libraries
- TL Strauss to Anderson (with attached note Strauss to Cole), 1957 August 9; 1 p. (Box 4, Folder 255)
- TL Cole to Martin, 1957 September 19; 2 pp. (Box 4, Folder 256)
- TL Cole to Hickenlooper, 1957 August 29; 1 p. (Box 4, Folder 256)
- TL Cole to Durham, 1957 August 29; 1 p. (Box 4, Folder 256)
- TL Cole to Anderson, 1957 August 14; 2 pp. (Box 4, Folder 257)
- TLS Jones to Cole, 1957 July 22; 1 p. (Box 4, Folder 257)
- TL Hickenlooper to Durham, 1957 July 26; 1 p. (Box 4, Folder 257)
- TL Charles Robbins to Cole, 1957 July 3; 1 p (Box 4, Folder 258)
- TL from Charles Robbins to William H. Stringer, 1957 July 9; 1 p (Box 4, Folder 258)
- TL from Earl H. Hammons to Cole, 1957 April 10; 1 p. (Box 4, Folder 258)
- TL Cole to Charles Robbins, 1957 July 11; 1 p (Box 4, Folder 259)
- Cole remarks at the Japan Forum, 1957 May 13; 3 p (Box 4, Folder 259)
- Cole remarks at Banquet given by Japan Atomic Industrial Forum in Tokyo, Japan, 1957 May 13; 2 pp. (Box 4, Folder 259)
- TL Earl Gammons to Sherman Adams, 1957 April 10; 1 p (Box 4, Folder 260A)
- TLS Norman Cousins to Cole, 1957 May 6; 1 p (Box 4, Folder 260A)
- TLS Lewis Strauss to Cole, 1957 June 26; 1 p. (Box 4, Folder 260A)
- TL Cole to William Mitchell, 1957 June 17; 1 p (Box 4, Folder 260B)
- TL Cole to Alden A. Potter, 1957 June 26; 1 p (Box 4, Folder 260B)
- TLS James J Wadsworth to Cole, 1957 April 29; 1 p. (Box 4, Folder 260B)
- TL Cole to James T. Ramey, 1957 June 21; 1 p (Box 4, Folder 261)
- Robert Woodbury to Joch Calkius, 1957 June 12; 1 p (Box 4, Folder 261)
- TL Cole to Editor of New York Times, 1957 April 30; 1 p. (Box 4, Folder 261)
- TLS Cole to J. Gerald Mayer, 1957 June 24; 1 p (Box 4, Folder 262)
- TLS J. Gerald Mayer to Cole, 1957 June 19; 1 p (Box 4, Folder 262)
- TLS Theodore R. McKeldin to Cole, 1957 March 21; 1 p. (Box 4, Folder 262)
- TL Cole to Dr. D. Guilford Dudley, 1957 April 23; 1 p (Box 4, Folder 263)
- TL Jesse C. Johnson to Cole, 1957 April 22; 1 p (Box 4, Folder 263)
- TL Cole to Jesse C. Johnson, 1957 April 15; 1 p (Box 4, Folder 263)
- TL D.G. Dudley to Cole, 1957 April 11; 1 p (Box 4, Folder 263)
- TL D.G. Dudley to Cole, 1957 April 11; 1 p (2 copies). (Box 4, Folder 263)
- TLS Charles G. Bolte to Cole, 1957 April 26; 1 p (Box 4, Folder 264)
- News and Notes of Books and Bookmen, 1957 April 23; 1 p (Box 4, Folder 264)
- TLS Cole to Carl T. Durham, 1957 April 8; 1 p. (Box 4, Folder 264)
- TL Davis to Picket, 1957 May 20; 3 pp. (Box 4, Folder 265)
- TL Cole to Smart, 1957 April 10; 1 p. (Box 4, Folder 265)
- TL Smart to Cole, 1957 April 3; 1 p. (Box 4, Folder 265)
- TL Cole to Jenkins, 1957 June 11; 1 p. (Box 4, Folder 266)
- TL Jenkins to Cole, 1957 June 3; 2 pp. (Box 4, Folder 266)
- Handwritten Letter, Mitchell to Cole, 1957 June 19; 1 p. (Box 4, Folder 266)
- TL Cole to June, 1957 June 4; 1 p. (Box 4, Folder 267)
- TLS June to Cole, 1957 May 8; 2 pp. (Box 4, Folder 267)
- TL Cole to Strauss, 1957 May 28; 1 p. (Box 4, Folder 267)
- TL Dudley to Cole, 1957 May 6; 1 p. (Box 4, Folder 267)
- Telegram Cole to Slater, undated; 1 p. (Box 4, Folder 268)
- Telegram Cole to Teller, 1957 June 21; 1 p. (Box 4, Folder 268)
- Telegram Cole to EO Lawrence, 1 p. (Box 4, Folder 268)
- Cole's Statement at his Presentation of wreath at Statue of Leopold FIGL with photograph, 1984 September 11; 5 pp. (Box 4, Folder 269)
- Statement prepared for Brazil and Not Used, 1960 July; 5 pp. (Box 4, Folder 270)
- Third Inter-American Symposium on the Peaceful uses of Atomic Energy, Rio de Janeiro, 1960 July 18-23; 5 pp. (Box 4, Folder 270)
- Fifth Regular Session of the General Conference, IAEA. Vienna, Austria, 1961 September 26 (Box 4, Folder 271)
  Rough Copies of Speech.
- International Seminar for Diplomats, 1960 March 22; 5 pp. (Box 4, Folder 272)
- Conference on Small and Medium Power Reactors, Vienna (Stadhalle), 1960 September 5; 4 pp. (Box 4, Folder 273)
- Conference on the Use of Radioisotopes in the Physical Sciences and Industry, 1960 September 6; 3 pp. (Box 4, Folder 274)
- Fourth General Conference, Hofburg, Vienna, 1960 September 20 (Box 4, Folder 275)
- National Council of the Churches of Christ, New York, New York, 1960 November 15 (Box 4, Folder 276)
- Annual Meeting of the European Energy Agency, Paris, France, 1960 November 24 (Box 4, Folder 277)
- Opening of Seibersdorf Reactor Station, Seiberdorf, Austria, 1960 September 29 (Box 4, Folder 278)
- TL Seligman to Galagan, 1960 October 27; 2 pp. (Box 4, Folder 279)
- Atomic Industrial Forum. San Francisco, CA, 1960 December 14; 2 drafts. (Box 4, Folder 280)
- Diplomatic Conference on Maritime Law. Brussels, Belgium, 1961 April 17 (Box 4, Folder 281)
- Inter-Governmental Committee on Civil Liability for Nuclear Damage, Vienna, 1961 May 3 (Box 4, Folder 282)
- Symposium on the Detection and use of Tritium in the Physical and Biological Sciences, Vienna, 1961 May 3; 4 pp. (Box 4, Folder 283)
- Nuclear Energy Exhibition. Belgrade, Yugoslavia, 1961 May 13; 3 pp. (Box 4, Folder 284)
- Conference on Nuclear Electronics. Belgrade, Yugoslavia, 1961 May 15 (Box 4, Folder 285)
- Symposium on the Effects of Ionizing Radiation on the Nervous System. Vienna, Austria, 1961 June 5 (Box 4, Folder 286)
- Inauguration of the Democritus Nuclear Research Center. Athens, Greece, 1961 July 31 (Box 4, Folder 287)
- Seminar on the Physics of the Fast and Intermediate Reactors. Vienna, Austria, 1961 August 3 (Box 4, Folder 288)
- Conference on Plasma Physics and Controlled Nuclear Fusion. Salzburg, Austria, 1961 September 4 (Box 4, Folder 289)
- TL J.F. Dulles to Cole, 1957 September 5; 2 pp. (Box 4, Folder 290)
- TLS Suchanek to Cole, 1961 October 30; 1 p. (Box 4, Folder 290)
- TL Cole to Raisic and Ristic, 1961 August 28; 1 p. (Box 4, Folder 291)
- Confirmation Telegram, unnamed, 1961 August 14; 1 p. (Box 4, Folder 291)
- TL Cole to Sarajoic, 1961 July 25; 2 pp. (Box 4, Folder 291)
- TL Cole to Sarajoic, 1961 June 21; 1 p. (Box 4, Folder 291)
- TL Cole to Bidiano, 1961 August 28; 1 p. (Box 4, Folder 292)
- TL Sanielevici to Cole, 1961 August 14; 1 p. (Box 4, Folder 292)
- TL Cole to Dimitriu, 1961 July 25; 2 pp. (Box 4, Folder 292)
- TL Dimitriu to Cole, 1961; 1 p. (Box 4, Folder 292)
- TL Cole to Dimitriu, 1961 June 21; 1 p. (Box 4, Folder 292)
- TL Cole to Uricky, Hollai and Kovari, 1961 August 29; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 293)
- TL Cole to Sebes, 1961 July 25; 2 pp. (Box 5, Folder 293)
- TL Sebes to Cole, 1961 June 30; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 293)
- TL Sebes to Cole, 1961 June 21; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 293)
- TL Cole to Davieson, 1960 January 25; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 294)
- TL Cole to Davis, 1960 January 25; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 294)
- TL Cole to Demut, 1958 February 12; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 294)
- TLS Devine to Cole, 1961 February 17; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 295)
- TL Cole to Daskalov, 1961 July 25; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 295)
- TL Cole to Jezek, 1961 July 25; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 295)
- TL Cole to de Hoffman, 1959 June 2; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 296)
- TL de Hoffman to Cole, 1959 May 7; 2 pp. (Box 5, Folder 296)
- TL Diamond to Cole, 1960 March 14; 2 pp. (Box 5, Folder 296)
- TLS Gregory to Cole, 1961 January 27; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 297)
- TLS TM Gregory and Co. to Cole, 1961 January 10; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 297)
- TL Cole to TM Gregory and Co., 1961 January 6; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 297)
- TLS W.S. Cole to Cole, 1955 October 29; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 297)
- TL Cole to D.A. Davies, 1961 November 13; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 298)
- TLS D.A. Davies to Cole, 1961 November 7; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 298)
- TL Willner to Papworth, 1961 July 21; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 299)
- TL Willner to Cole, 1961 July 7; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 299)
- TL Willner to Cole, 1961 July 7; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 299)
- TL Travel Unit to Cole, 1961 June 15; 2 pp. (Box 5, Folder 299)
- TL Cole to Zwicker, 1961 August 2; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 299)
  (English/German)
- TL Cole to Burgermeister, 1961 August 2; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 300)
- TLS Zwicker to Cole, 1961 July 22; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 300)
- TLS Mayor to Cole, 1961 July 20; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 300)
- TLS Burgermeister to Cole, 1961 June 28; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 300)
- TLS Willner to Papworth, 1961 July 19; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 300)
- Correspondence between the Davidsons and Coles, RE: Music Tapes and Personal, 1958 April 24-1961 February 18; 5 letters (Box 5, Folder 301)
- RE: Travel Plans for Mr. and Mrs. Hammer, 1961 November 10-1961 June 26; 5 letters (Box 5, Folder 302)
- RE: Travel Plans for Harley E. Brainard, 1962 November 10-1961 January 20; 15 letters (Box 5, Folder 303)
- Correspondence between Friedrich Ponath, Captain L. Suchanek and Cole. RE: Danube Trip, 1961 July 26-1961 September 14; 8 letters (Box 5, Folder 304)
- TL Cole to Doan, 1961 January 3; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 305)
- TLS Doan to Cole, 1960 December 20; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 305)
- TLS Dowding to Cole, 1959 March 30; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 305)
- TL Cole to Dowding, 1959 March 13; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 305)
- TLS Vedeler to Cole, 1959 June 9; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 306)
- TL Cole to J.F. Dulles, 1959 February 19; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 306)
- TL Cole to Duran, 1961 October 27; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 306)
- TLS Duran to Cole, 1961 October 16; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 306)
- Correspondence between Carl Durham and Cole, 1958 March 18-1960 May 24; 13 letters (Box 5, Folder 307)
- TLS Herter to Cole, 1958 June 26; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 308)
- TL Armand to J.F. Dulles, 1958 June 23; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 308)
- TL Cole to Evans, 1959 January 8; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 308)
- TL Cole to Faber, 1959 February 11; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 309)
- TL Cole to Fahmy, 1959 February 17; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 309)
- TL Cole to Mrs. Fahmy, 1959 February 10; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 309)
- Correspondence with and about the Fabers, 1958 January 14-1958 July 9; 15 letters (Box 5, Folder 310)
- TL Cole to Fast, 1958 August 27; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 311)
- TLS Fast to Cole, 1958 August 1; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 311)
- TLS Floberg to Cole, 1958 December 11; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 311)
- TLS Jolles to Cole, 1961 January 30; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 312)
- TL D.A.V. Fischer to Jolles, 1961 January 30; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 312)
- TL Cole to HFS Bittencourt, 1961 January 26; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 312)
- Correspondence with WM Fechtler, 1958 December 31-1960 August 26; 3 letters (Box 5, Folder 313)
- Correspondence with Josephine Floyd, 1958 July 10-1958 July 28; 4 letters (Box 5, Folder 314)
- Correspondence with Frank M. Folsom, 1958 February 25-1960 July 4; 23 letters (Box 5, Folder 315)
- Correspondence with Dr. Alwyn V. Freeman, 1958 May 27-1961 April 19; 40 letters (Box 5, Folder 316)
- Correspondence with Yoshio Fujioka, 1958 December 15-1959 January 9; 3 letters (Box 5, Folder 317)
- TLS Furuuchi to Cole, 1959 December 10; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 318)
- TLS Furuuchi to Cole, 1957 December 19; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 318)
- Correspondence with Andrey Galagan, 1958 February 18-1961 October30; 16 letters (Box 5, Folder 319)
- TL Cole to Gabrielli, 1961 October 19; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 320)
- TLS Gabrielli to Cole, 1961 October 9; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 320)
- TLS Gabrielli to Cole, 1959 April 27; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 320)
- TL Cole to Gannet, 1957 October 21; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 321)
- TLS Gannet to Cole, 1957 October 30; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 321)
- TL Cole to McCone, 1959 January 21; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 322)
- TL Cole to Strauss, 1959 January 21; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 322)
- TL Cole to Strauss, 1960 January 28; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 322)
- TL Cole to Strauss, 1959 October 5; 2 pp. (Box 5, Folder 322)
- TLS Strauss to Cole, 1959 October 2; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 322)
- Correspondence Re: Lewis Strauss' Resignation, 1959 June 27-1959 July 7; 3 letters and 1 article (Box 5, Folder 323)
- TLS RW Cook to Cole, 1958 May 22; 2 pp. (Box 5, Folder 324)
- TLS Strauss to Cole, 1958 May 21; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 324)
- TL Cole to Strauss, 1958 May 15; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 324)
- TLS Strauss to Cole, 1957 December 13; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 325)
- TL Cole to Strauss, 1957 December 21; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 325)
- TL Cole to Pastore, 1961 March 6; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 325)
- TL Cole to Holifield, 1961 March 6; 3 pp. (Box 5, Folder 326a)
- TL Cole to Graham, 1961 February 8; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 326a)
- TLS Graham to Cole, 1961 February 3; 2 pp. (Box 5, Folder 326a)
- TL Cole to Graham, 1961 January 26; 2 pp. (Box 5, Folder 326b)
- TL Cole to Wilson, 1961 January 26; 2 pp. (Box 5, Folder 326b)
- TLS McCone to Cole, 1961 February 6; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 326b)
- TL Cole to De Michele, 1960 December 21; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 327)
- TLS Foster to Cole, 1960 September 6; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 327)
- TLD McCone to Cole, 1961 August 25; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 327)
- TLS Wells to Cole, 1960 April 27; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 328a)
- TL Cole to Wells, 1960 April 21; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 328a)
- TL Cole to Strauss, 1958 July 29; 3 pp. (Box 5, Folder 328b)
- TL Cole to Strauss, 1959 June 2; 2 pp. (Box 5, Folder 328b)
- TL Cole to Strauss, 1959 July 16; 3 pp. (Box 5, Folder 328b)
- TL Cole to James E. Van Zandt, 1960 April 25; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 329)
- TLS B.B. Hickenlooper, 1960 April 26; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 329)
- TL Cole to Bourke B. Hickenlooper, 1960 April 21; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 329)
- TL Cole to Chet Holifield, 1960 April 25; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 330)
- TL Cole to Carl Durham, 1960 April 25; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 330)
- TL Cole to John O. Pastore, 1960 April 21; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 330)
- TLS John McCone to Cole, 1960 September 24; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 331)
- TL Cole to John McCone, 1961 January 26; 2 pp. (Box 5, Folder 331)
- TLS John A. McCone to Cole, 1961 January 19; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 331)
- TLS Jesse C. Johnson to Cole, 1960 April 18; 2 pp. (Box 5, Folder 332)
- TLS Francis O. Wilcox to Cole, 1961 January 24; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 332)
- TLS Chester Bowles to Cole, 1961 April 10; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 332)
- TLS Courts Oulahan to Cole, 1961 May 8; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 333)
- TLS Eugene M. Zuckert to Cole, 1961 February 16; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 333)
- TL Cole to Eugene Zuckert, 1961 February 7; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 333)
- TLS Douglas Dillon to Cole, 1961 March 6; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 334)
- TL Cole to Douglas Dillon, 1961 February 10; 2 pp. (Box 5, Folder 334)
- TLS Paul F. Foster to Cole, 1959 December 4; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 334)
- Correspondence with Paul Foster, 1959 May 18-1961 February 10; 7 letters (Box 5, Folder 335)
- Correspondence with Robert McKinney, 1958 March 12-1958 October 6; 6 letters (Box 5, Folder 336)
- TL Cole to Harold C. Vedeler, 1958 May 13; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 337)
- TLS Harold C. Vedeler to Cole, 1958 May 6; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 337)
- "Agreement for Cooperation," USA-IAEA, 4 pp. (Box 5, Folder 337)
- TLS Henry Labouisse to Cole, 1961 February 22; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 338)
- TL Cole to Henry R. Labouisse, 1961 February 6; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 338)
- TLS Harlan Cleveland to Cole, 1961 February 21; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 339)
- TL Cole to James H. Cleveland, 1961 February 6; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 339)
- TL Cole to Dean Rusk, 1961 February 10; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 339)
- Telegram Dean Rusk to Cole, 1961; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 339)
- TL Herter to Unknown Recipient, 1958 May 30; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 339)
- TL Cole to Dan A. Kimball, 1958 February 11; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 340)
- TLS Dan A. Kimball to Cole, 1958 February 4; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 340)
- TL Cole to Senator and Mrs. Warren R. Austin, 1958 December 18; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 340)
- TLS George Anderson, Jr. to Cole, undated; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 341)
- TL Cole to George Anderson, 1961 July 4; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 341)
- TL Cole to George H. Allen, Jr., 1958 July 29; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 341)
- "Remarks of Senator Clinton P. Anderson before the congressional Club", 1960 January 15; 11 pp. (Box 5, Folder 342)
- TL Cole to Clinton P. Anderson, 1957 November 5; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 342)
- TLS Clinton P. Anderson to Cole, 1957 November 1; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 342)
- TL Cole to Kay Allardice, 1961 March 9; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 343)
- TL Cole to Corbin Allardice, 1961 February 10; 2 pp. (Box 5, Folder 343)
- TLS Corbin Allardice to Cole, 1961 February 2; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 343)
- TL Cole to Corbin C. Allardice, 1959 March 24; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 343)
- TL Cole to George L. Weil, 1959 February 25; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 343)
- Telegram Cole to Unknown Recipient, 1959 February 25; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 343)
- TLS George L. Weil to Cole, 1959 February 20; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 343)
- TL Cole to Vice Admiral G.F. Hussey, Jr. USN (Ret.), 1957 December 20; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 344)
- TLS G.F. Jussey, Jr. to Cole, 1957 December 16; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 344)
- TLS Rev. George H. Allen, Jr. to Cole, 1958 June 10; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 344)
- Correspondence regarding Doris Andrew as a Post master, 1959 May 19-1966 June 2; 6 letters (Box 5, Folder 345)
- TL Cole to Janice Angell, 1958 July 24; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 346)
- TLS Janice Angell to Cole, 1958 June 26; 2 pp. (Box 5, Folder 346)
- TL Cole to Janice Angell, 1958 May 30; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 346)
- Antiques collection, 1960; 2 booklets and 4 receipts (Box 5, Folder 347)
- TLS Nazir Ahmad to Cole, 1960 April 15; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 348)
- TL Cole to Nazir Ahmad, 1960 February 23; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 348)
- TLS Carl W. Larsen to Ned Traprell, 1957 November 12; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 348)
- TL John Bell to Carl Larsen, 1957 November 7; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 348)
- TLS Edwin T. O'Donnel, 1959 February 20; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 349)
- TL Cole to Army and Navy Country Club, 1959 February 11; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 349)
- Bulletin, "Army and Navy Country Club", undated; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 349)
- Correspondence with Mr. Percy Leason, in regards to portraits, 1956 June 22-1959 February 23; 12 letters (Box 5, Folder 350)
- TL Lewis Wilson to Cole, 1958 May 14; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 351)
- TL Cole to Lewis Wilson, 1958 July 22 (Box 5, Folder 351)
- TLS Lewis A. Wilson to Cole, 1958 July 17; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 351)
- Correspondence with Ludwig F. Audrieth, 1957 November 21-1965 June 22; 7 letters (Box 5, Folder 352)
- Correspondence with Robert Austin, 1958 June 20-1960 November 28; 6 letters (Box 5, Folder 353)
- TL Cole to Mr. Roger Forst de Battaglia, March 24; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 354)
- TL Cole to Mary Mayhew Einstein, 1960 February 22; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 354)
- TLS Walter Riehlman to Cole, 1960 February 5; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 354)
- TL Cole to Charles Robbins, 1961 October 4; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 355)
- TLS Charles Robbins to Cole, 1961 September 28; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 355)
- TL Cole to Charles Robbins, 1961 August 28; 2 pp. (Box 5, Folder 355)
- TLS Charles Robbins to Cole, 1961 August 17; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 355)
- "G" (Box 5, Folder 356)
- AL William Gay to Cole, 1961 August 18; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 356)
- TL Cole to Mr. William D. Gay, 1961 July 3; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 356)
- TL Cole to Mr. William Gay, 1959 January 7; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 356)
- TL Cole to Mr. William Gay, 1958 January 17; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 356)
- TL Cole to Mr. William D. Gay, 1957 December 3; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 356)
- TLS William Gay to Cole, 1957 November 29; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 356)
- TL Cole to Paul Genachte, 1958 January 21 (Box 5, Folder 356)
- TLS Paul Genachte to Cole, 1957 December 16; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 356)
- TLS Keith Glennan to Cole, 1958 September 8; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 356)
- TL Cole to Mr. T. Keith Glennan, 1958 August 27; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 356)
- TLS T. Keith Glennan to Cole, 1958 August 12; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 356)
- TL Cole to Mrs. Walter M. Goff, 1961 April 4; 2 pp. (Box 5, Folder 356)
- AL Goff to Cole, 1959 July 13; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 356)
- TL Cole to Mr. Walter M. Goff, 1959 June 30; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 356)
- TL Cole to Bertrand Goldschmidt, 1961 November 15; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 356)
- TL Cole to Clark Goodman, 1961 November 27; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 356)
- TLS Clark Goodman to Cole, 1961 October 24; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 356)
- TL Cole to Clark Goodman, 1961 October 19; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 356)
- Telegram Clark Goodman to Cole, 1961 October 10; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 356)
- TLS Clark Goodman to Cole, 1961 October 4; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 356)
- Greece Atomic Energy Commission. Photographs, Democritus Monument at Abdera (Box 5, Folder 356)
- TL Cole to Madame Mary C. Carolon, 1960 August 18; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 356)
- TLS Mary C. Carolon to Cole, 1960 July 14; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 356)
- Pamphlet, "Address of H.M. The Queen on the Occasion of a Lecture," Professor Dr. W.K. Heisenberg, 1960 March 6; 4 pp. (Box 5, Folder 356)
- TL Cole to Charles S. Gubser, 1959 January 23; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 356)
- TLS Charles A. Gubser to Cole, 1959 January 17; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 356)
- TL Cole to Charles S. Gubser, 1959 January 8; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 356)
- TLS Charles S. Gubser to Cole, 1958 December 5; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 356)
- TL from Cole to Mr. and Mrs. N.T. Gulrajani, 1961 October 9; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 356)
- TLS N.T. Gulrajani to Cole, 1960 December 13; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 356)
- Business Card, N.T. Gulrajani. (Box 5, Folder 356)
- "K" (Box 5, Folder 357)
- AL Elsa Maria Kafka to Cole, 1958 October 12; 4 pp. (Box 5, Folder 357)
- TL Cole to Dan Kearney, 1961 April 12; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 357)
- TLS Dan Kearney to Cole, 1961 March 15; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 357)
- TL Cole to "Madam" (Secretary to Mrs. John Kennedy), 1961 August 10; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 357)
- TLS Kenneth B. Keating to Cole, 1958 September 25; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 357)
- TL Cole to Mr. Itzhak Keenan, 1961 November 27; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 357)
- TL Cole to Mr. Kilburn, 1961 September 25; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 357)
- TL Cole to Clarence E. Kilburn, 1961 August 28; 2 pp. (Box 5, Folder 357)
- TLS Clarence E. Kilburn to Cole, 1961 August 16; 2 pp. (Box 5, Folder 357)
- TL Cole to Clarence E. Kilburn, 1959 August 26; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 357)
- TLS Clarence E. Kilburn, 1959 August 18; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 357)
- TLS Clarence E. Kilburn to Cole, 1958 September 30; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 357)
- TL Dan A. Kimball to Lewis Strauss, 1957 December 10; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 357)
- TL Cole to Herschel Burt King, 1957 December 13; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 357)
- TLS Herschel Burt King to Cole, 1957 November 16; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 357)
- Post card, view from Mountain Top, near Elmira, N.Y. (Box 5, Folder 357)
- TLS Eric Kissmeyer to Cole, 1961 October 19; 2 pp. (Box 5, Folder 357)
- TLS Eric K. Nielsen to Cole, 1958 August 29; 2 pp. (Box 5, Folder 357)
- TL Cole to Mr. E. Kissmeyer-Nielsen, 1958 August 26; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 357)
- TLS Eric Kissmeyer-Nielsen to Cole, 1958 August 10; 2 pp. (Box 5, Folder 357)
- TL Cole to Walter E. Kingston, 1958 October 16; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 357)
- TLS Walter E. Kingston to Cole, 1958 October 8; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 357)
- TLS Hans Koch to Cole, 1960 September 26; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 357)
- TL Cole to Mihaly Kokeny, 1960 January 7; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 357)
- Telegram Unknown Sender to Cole, no year December 31; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 357)
- TL Peider Konz to Cole, 1958 November 12; 2 pp. (Box 5, Folder 357)
- TLS Joseph Ku to Cole, 1960 February 2; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 357)
- TLS Joseph Ku to Cole, 1959 November 24; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 357)
- TL Cole to Joseph Ku, 1959 November 13; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 357)
- TLS Joseph Ku to Cole, 1959 November 5; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 357)
- TL Cole to John C. Kunkel, 1961 May 29; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 357)
- Article from Washington (AP) regarding John C. Kunkel. (Box 5, Folder 357)
- "L" (Box 5, Folder 358)
- TL Hubert de Laboulaye to Cole, 1960 November 4; 3 pp. (Box 5, Folder 358)
- TL Cole to Hylov and deLaboulaye, 1960 November 2; 2 pp. (Box 5, Folder 358)
- TL Hans Henrik Koch to Cole, 1960 October 19; 2 pp. (Box 5, Folder 358)
- TL P.R. Jolles to Professor Rolf Sievert, 1960 November 2; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 358)
- TL Hubert deLaboulaye to Professor J. Kaufman, 1960 October 27; 2 pp. (Box 5, Folder 358)
- TL Cole to Hubert deLaboulaye, 1953 December 18; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 358)
- TL Cole to Jay LeFevre, 1958 April 5; 1 p. (Box 5, Folder 358)